Throughout your career as an entrepreneur,
what has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
24 million this year.
And what's the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single month?
A single month was 2.9 million.
Have you ever been broke before?
Hell yes.
And I wake up every morning, I feel broke.
Fuck yeah.
I lost $12 million in a year
and I went to Vegas with $100.
You know what I did?
I cracked over $100 million in one year, 2021.
How can someone become wealthy going into 2024?
Pay attention, guys.
It's 1,700 millionaires created every single day.
Any one of us can be one on Monday, Tuesday,
Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday.
Fun fact, I became one
of those millionaires on a Tuesday,
a random Tuesday.
So if I know I can do
it, you can do it as well
because nothing about me fit the millionaire description.
Give them the 60 second blueprint
to becoming a multimillionaire
like yourself in today's world.
I mean, everyone says.
The city of Miami, Florida is home
to over 38,000 millionaires.
And today we're gonna be
going all over the entire city
asking these multimillionaires how they became wealthy
and how you can start your path
to becoming financially free going into 2024.
And with that being said, let's
get the video on the way.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career in?
Real estate.
I've been involved in buying and selling
of over 20 billion worth of assets.
So I've bought personally probably 12 billion
worth of apartments that I've turned around
and sold 18, 19 billion.
What has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
Over a hundred million a year.
Over a hundred million dollars.
And that's for the business or?
Well, I own the business.
And so, yeah, those are S-corp returns
that hit my personal balance sheet.
How old are you now?
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
Probably 25.
Have you ever been broke before?
Hell yes.
And I wake up every morning, I feel broke.
But yeah, I mean, I remember when I first started,
I would go to the ATM on a Friday
and yank out all my money
because I know after five o'clock on Friday,
it would be in the red.
So I literally was like,
it felt like stealing money to survive,
through the weekends.
I would have 10 single family construction deals,
the same robbing from Peter to pay Paul.
That's all I did.
I mean, I would pay myself a development fee
and live off that
and then borrow another development fee.
And so, hell yeah.
I think if you've never felt broke before,
you don't have a healthy enough fear.
It's like a guy that thinks he's a tough guy
that's never had his ass kicked.
Yeah.
You hear the saying,
the rich get richer, the poor get poor.
For somebody who may be
stuck in that cycle of poverty,
what is an actionable step
that they can take to break out of that?
One, you got to do it.
You got to have the balls to do it.
Now is a perfect time.
There's a huge reset in wealth right now.
Commercial real estate is down at least 30, 40%.
The stock market in general has been down 30, 40%.
High tech, you know,
with huge multiple valuations are down more than 30, 40%.
So every financial asset,
because of interest rates,
is down 30, 40%.
So that's a pretty nice starting place
when people are down 30, 40%.
All right.
Now they're dealing with their own problems
and people are looking for solutions.
Capital is not needed right now.
Solutions are.
Go work with lenders.
Go to foreclosure.
Single family homes
that nobody wants to screw with
and take them on the property management
and say, hey, if I fix it up,
give me 10% of the profits.
There's a bunch of different
ways to get in the game
or befriend a very wealthy person
and be his number two
and have him throw you in deals.
That's the shortcut.
Beautiful interview, man.
That was phenomenal, man.
Appreciate you, bro.
My guy, Patrick, made over
$100 million in a single year,
not the business, but himself personally,
because he built one of the largest real estate companies
in all of Miami.
He's raised and sold billions and billions of dollars.
And that's why he's been able to do $20 billion.
Worth a real estate transaction over his career.
An absolutely phenomenal interview.
Let's go get this next one.
All right, you guys, my guy
just pulled up in the Cullen
and out in Miami, Florida.
We got to go to
and see what this guy did
to be able to own
a Rolls out here in Miami.
Let's see what he has to say.
Excuse me, bro.
Quick question for you, man.
Is this your Rolls Royce?
Yes, sir.
And what do you do for a living?
How are you able to afford
a Rolls out in Miami, Florida?
I'm in e-commerce.
You're in e-commerce.
How long have you been in the business for?
Since 2018.
Over that period of time,
what's the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
In a single year, 9.7 million.
9.7 million dollars.
And how did you take your business
from six to seven figures?
Oh, man, I had to implement those systems, you know,
because I went broke three times behind
starting a business and everything.
And every time I went broke,
it was because I lacked something.
Branding, marketing, systems.
So branding took me to six figures.
Marketing took me to seven figures.
Systems took me to eight figures.
We go all over the country asking business owners
their advice to young entrepreneurs.
Can we ask you a
few questions outside of the car?
Let's do it.
Awesome, let's run it.
What is the most common misconception
that people have about wealth in today's world?
Man, listen.
Pay attention, guys.
It's 1,700 millionaires created every single day.
Any one of us can
be one on Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday,
Thursday, Friday, Saturday.
Fun fact, I became one
of those millionaires on a Tuesday.
A random Tuesday.
Wasn't special, wasn't a holiday.
It was a random Tuesday.
So if I know I can do
it, you can do it as well
because nothing about me fit the millionaire description,
right?
I was just a lazy guy working a job
that was only paying me $8 an hour
until I said I have to do something
and I have to change my life.
So I don't want nobody to think
that this is just something that's made
for only a few people in the world.
Yes, it's the top 1%,
but remember, 99% of people either don't know
or not trying to actually become an active millionaire.
So remember, 1,700 and you can
be one any day of the week.
Nobody is coming to save you.
Nobody came to save me.
When I passed out from
walking to my nine to five,
I used to walk two
miles to work every single day
because every car I bought was
a buy here, pay here car.
You know, the cars that was $300, $400, $500
break down on me quick, right?
To the point where I'm walking to work.
When I was on that pavement, passed out,
and I got up, my face red,
and everything, nobody was around.
People were just passing by in their cars.
If they didn't care if I lived or died,
it let me know right there
about what world we live in.
I realized, yo, it's all on me
and every decision is all on you.
We have the resources.
You just lack resourcefulness.
Get a nine to five, use that money
to actually put into the business,
get those products and make it happen.
And one of those 1,700 millionaires,
one day is gonna be your day.
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday,
hopefully Saturday, right?
That's crazy, yo.
Like I just laid out the blueprint
for everybody trying to start making that money
going into 2024.
1,700 millionaires are created every single day.
It doesn't matter what day of the week it is.
There's so much money and opportunity out there
for you guys.
Just take action.
You can make this shit happen.
Shout out to him.
Let's go get this next one.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career in?
I pursued a career in a couple industries.
My big business was addiction and mental health treatment,
but also real estate and a few other investments.
What has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
I cracked over $100 million in one year.
2021, hell yeah.
What's the most common mistake
that people make with their money
that keeps them bright?
The most common mistake they make with their money
is that they have a poor mindset.
They make the money, they make earned income,
even if it's a lot of earned income,
and they spend it on their lifestyle.
They need to stop, make the money,
invest that into cash-flowing assets,
aka real estate for those who are not following along,
and then live off of the
cash flow from the real estate.
And so let me break that down one more time.
Poor mindset.
Make the money, spend it on the dinners,
the cars, the accessories,
the expensive penthouse, the whatever.
That's poor people shit.
What rich people do is they make the money,
they have financial discipline,
they have patience,
and they invest it into cash-flowing appreciating assets.
If you don't know those words,
cash-flowing appreciating assets,
you're already in trouble.
And those produce cash,
and then they live off
of that cash flow in perpetuity.
That is called financial freedom.
That is how you're gonna stack up.
Fuck you, money.
Going into 2024,
give somebody the blueprint
to becoming a nine-figure entrepreneur.
How can someone become wealthy?
Going into 2024.
They have to find whatever their thing is, right?
Find your thing and have a blueprint and a roadmap.
There's a couple different things at risk here
is that people don't have a design
for how they're gonna get there.
They have no fucking plan.
They're playing checkers, not chess.
That shit is crazy.
You're gonna be 15 moves ahead.
I know what I'm doing month over month
for the next five years
trying to crack that billionaire level.
Let me give you another little golden nugget.
This is where most of you guys fuck up.
You guys think it happens fast,
and then you don't look at the long term.
You need to have macro patience and micro urgency.
What you guys have is micro patience and macro urgency.
And what I mean by
that is you need to know
that this is gonna take a long time.
People look at my life
and they don't see the 17 fucking years
that happened before I was out here in Miami
living this life.
And so they miscalibrate on how long it's gonna take.
They think it's gonna happen faster than it is.
Every single fucking day,
you give it absolutely everything that you have to give.
That's how you win.
Come on, bro.
We're about to run it up again.
So we pulled up in
the design district in Miami, Florida,
and Eric Spofford, the nine figure entrepreneur
that sold a business for more than $100 million,
pulled up on us.
And he just gave you guys the blueprint right there.
You have to become an expert
and the best in the world at one thing.
Otherwise, you're gonna get slaughtered
in this game of business.
Shout out to Eric.
Let's go get this next one, man.
Throughout your career,
what's been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
In a month?
The best I've ever done?
$550,000 in a single month.
Are you a business owner?
What the fuck do you
think I'd do for a living?
Of course.
How long have you been a business owner for?
Since I was 22.
And how old are you now?
What's the name of your company?
I can tell you that.
You don't have to, okay.
Have you ever been broke before?
Fuck yeah.
I went to Vegas for $100.
I lost $12 million in a year,
and I went to Vegas with $100.
$103, actually.
My brother borrowed me $2,500.
You know what I did?
The smartest thing you do in Vegas,
I put it all in black.
And I won.
And then I won.
Then I won three times.
Then I started working again.
For somebody stuck in that cycle of poverty,
you hear the saying that rich get richer,
the poor get poorer.
That's bullshit.
For somebody, it is.
That is such a bullshit.
We are living in America, the land of opportunity.
Everybody can have three jobs
and invest and make a deal
and make something out of it.
Especially right now, you kids are so inventing everything.
That's bullshit.
If you broke because you want to be fucking broke.
So how can someone escape poverty then?
How can someone become a multi-millionaire like yourself?
Give them the blueprint.
You kids, don't go crazy with the money
because nothing ever lasts.
It's like the baseball players, you know?
They all fucking broke.
Why'd they go broke?
Because their career only lasts fucking 10,
12 years.
After that, what the fuck are they gonna do?
Nothing.
That's why they all broke
because they don't know what to do next.
My advice to kids nowadays,
mature the business that you're doing.
Do a lot of numbers.
Make sure what is it selling out there
and save your money and keep thinking about innovating.
You have to innovate all the time,
especially now with the internet,
with all the apps nowadays.
You have to innovate all the time.
All right, you guys, my guy went from being broke
to making over $500,000 in a single month.
But I love how he cut
me off when I asked him
about the cycle of poverty.
It's not a cycle.
It's all a mindset.
Anybody can break out of it.
There's more opportunity in this country
than anywhere else in the entire planet.
Guy gave an amazing interview.
We're gonna go get this next one, man.
Miami's been unreal.
All right, you guys, we are at the number one
private jet airport in all of Miami, Florida.
And we're here to interview Wes Watson.
He said, pull up.
I wanna drop some game
for all the entrepreneurs out there.
If y'all know Wes, you know
that he's one of the baddest
and realest motherfuckers in the entire game.
With that being said, let's go
see what Wes has to say.
Have you ever been broke before?
Oh man, I was in prison for 10 years.
Hell yeah, I was broke.
I was eating Top Ramen
for 10 fucking years.
What has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
24 million this year.
24 million dollars this year.
24 million dollars.
And what's the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single month?
A single month was 2.9 million.
Now how did you go
from making seven to eight figures?
A lot of entrepreneurs will have that great idea.
They don't know how to scale.
This is what I did differently
than every other entrepreneur in my space.
Get around motherfuckers who think it's okay
to have $500,000 a month in expenses,
a million dollars a month in expenses.
Get around motherfuckers who pay 50 Gs
to fly to the speaking event
and come back in the same fucking day.
Get around motherfuckers who do not settle.
The richest people, they're not afraid to use money
as a tool to grow their wealth,
to grow their earned income, not only passive.
A lot of people just talk about passive income.
Earned income is what the top people have.
We talk about Bezos, we talk about Musk.
We're not saying, hey, his real estate portfolio.
We're like, Amazon makes X amount a day, motherfucker.
What has been the best financial advice
that you've ever received throughout your lifetime?
Brad Lee told me, the double R in the headrest
stands for recurring revenue.
Build it.
What is your best self-improvement advice
for people trying to get their life on track?
They want to become financially free
and successful like yourself.
The two things in life I tell people,
be the man you always
needed, be the customer you want.
Buy fast, don't ask a bunch of questions,
don't be a headache, do your research on the forefront,
and be the man you always needed.
Everything that everyone dropped the ball on
when you grew up, don't do that shit.
And that's what my company's based on.
The company's based on the fact that I'll never miss.
Because everybody else talked a big game,
but they weren't consistent.
They don't teach that in school, everybody.
Wes, thank you so much for letting us come out.
That was fun. Hell yeah.
All right, bro.
So, give them this right now, young 20-year-old kid,
they want to get serious about becoming financially free,
give them the 60-second blueprint
to becoming a multi-millionaire
like yourself in today's world.
I mean, everyone says, do what you love.
I'm just going to say,
nothing in this world is going to work for you.
You got to work for it.
So pick the path of the people that you see
that you want to be like,
and don't take no for an answer.
When I was in prison, I saw Instagram.
I did my first post on Instagram while in prison.
I told a guy next to
me on his rack, I said,
I'm going to be a multi-millionaire off this app,
which was Instagram.
I posted every day on Instagram till I got out.
By the time I got out, I had 10,000 followers.
I've never missed a post on Instagram or YouTube
or anything since then.
I saw it as the
greatest marketing tool known to man.
And I loved what people were putting on there.
They were doing workouts.
They were giving positive advice.
I needed to be part of that.
It made me feel so fucking good.
So I chased something that I really loved
and something that I needed.
I sell what I need.
I don't just sell anything people will buy.
And the first time I ever interviewed you,
you talked about the importance of creating those habits.
Show me your habits.
I'll tell you your future.
Break that down for people that may not understand
the importance of those daily habits.
I mean, the daily habits.
Show me your habits.
I'll tell your future.
I got to get up early.
When I get up early, I get up at 2.45.
And like I like to say, I'm first up.
That means I'm first place.
That's that first place mentality.
That's that winning mentality.
I train every day, make sure
that every day I'm in the gym
at least once, if not twice, three times a day.
And then we keep the nutrition on point.
But most of all, we work with others.
The two things that I do every day
is peak physical performance to get
in that positive mental state.
And the next thing is being
the source of what you see.
I literally can't live without serving others.
And that's the gift.
That had to be one of the craziest experiences
of my entire life running this channel.
Wes Watson tells us to pull
up to the private jet airport
before he flies out to Dallas, Texas.
And he says, let me tell you something.
I want to drop some bombs
and some game for all the young
entrepreneurs out there.
Wes is as real as they get.
But this Miami video was absolutely insane.
So be sure to like, subscribe
for amazing content on the way.
And click here to watch our
full video going all over Dallas
asking multimillionaires how they became wealthy.